{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Hello!",
      "answer": "Hey there!"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Frodo Baggins?",
      "answer": "He is a Hobbit who carried THE RING from the Shire to Mount Doom and destroyed it there."
    },
    {
      "question": "who is the nephew of bilbo baggins?",
      "answer": "Frodo Baggins."
    },
    {
      "question": "nephew of bilbo baggins",
      "answer": "Frodo Baggins"
    },
    {
      "question": "is frodo the nephew of bilbo",
      "answer": "yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "Frodo's best friend",
      "answer": "Samwise Gamgee."
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Frodo Baggins' best friend",
      "answer": "Samwise Gamgee."
    },
    {
      "question": "Hello there!",
      "answer": "Hello right back at you!"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Sam Gamgee?",
      "answer": "A Hobbit from the Shire and Frodo Baggins' best friend."
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Gandalf?",
      "answer": "A wizard, also called Istar. He watches over Middle-Earth. (And is a troublemaker.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "Where do Hobbits live?",
      "answer": "In the shire."
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Bag End?",
      "answer": "Bag End is the dwelling of Bilbo Baggins (and later of Frodo Baggins, too). One can find it in Hobbiton, a village in the shire."
    }
  ]
}